<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2 on Peng Zhao</title>
    <link>/en/publication_types/2/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2 on Peng Zhao</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Peng Zhao</copyright>
    <atom:link href="/en/publication_types/2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Castelli, M.; Anderson, M.; Yang, Y.; Wohlfahrt, G.; Bertoldi, G.; Niedrist, G.; Hammerle, A.; Zhao, P.; Zebisch, M. &amp; Notarnicola, C. Two-source energy balance modeling of evapotranspiration in Alpine grasslands Remote Sensing of Environment , 2018, 209, 327 - 342.</title>
      <link>/en/publication/castelli2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/publication/castelli2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zhao, P., and Lüers J.. 2017. Parameterization of Evapotranspiration Estimation for Two Typical East Asian Crops. Atmosphere 8 (6): 111.</title>
      <link>/en/publication/zhao2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/publication/zhao2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huang, S.,  Wang Y., Xie, Y., Zhao, P.*, and Lüers, J.. 2016. OutlierFlag: A Tool for Scientific Data Quality Control by Outlier Data Flagging. Journal of Open Research Software 4: e20. </title>
      <link>/en/publication/huang2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/publication/huang2016/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lee, C. B., Kim, J. C., Belorid, M., and Zhao, P.. 2016. Performance Evaluation of Four Different Land Surface Models in WRF. Asian Journal of Atmospheric Environment 10 (1): 42–50.</title>
      <link>/en/publication/lee2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/publication/lee2016/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wohlfahrt, G., Hammerle, A., Niedrist,G., Scholz, K., Tomelleri, E., and Zhao, P.. 2016. On the Energy Balance Closure and Net Radiation in Complex Terrain. Agricultural and Forest Meteorology 226 – 227: 37–49.</title>
      <link>/en/publication/wohlfahrt2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/publication/wohlfahrt2016/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zhao, P., and Lüers J.. 2016. Improved Data Gap-Filling Schemes for Estimation of Net Ecosystem Exchange in Typical East-Asian Croplands. Science China Earth Sciences, 1–13. </title>
      <link>/en/publication/zhao2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/publication/zhao2016/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zhao, P., and Lüers, J.. 2012. Improved Determination of Daytime Net Ecosystem Exchange of Carbon Dioxide at Croplands. Biogeosciences Discussions 9: 2883–2919.</title>
      <link>/en/publication/zhao2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/publication/zhao2012/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zhang, X., Wang, Y., Zhang, X., Guo, W., Niu, T., Gong, S., Yin,Y., Zhao, P., Jin, J., and Yu M.. 2008. Aerosol Monitoring at Multiple Locations in China: Contributions of EC and Dust to Aerosol Light Absorption. Tellus B 60 (4). Wiley Online Library: 647–56.</title>
      <link>/en/publication/zhang2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/publication/zhang2008/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zhao, P., Zhu T., Liang, B., Hu, M., Kang, L., and Gong J.. 2007. Characteristics of Mass Distributions of Aerosol Particle and Its Inorganic Water-Soluble Ions in Summer over a Suburb Farmland in Beijing. Frontiers of Environmental Science and Engineering in China 1 (2). Springer: 159–65.</title>
      <link>/en/publication/zhao2007/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/publication/zhao2007/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zhao, P., Zhu, T., Liang, B., Hu, M., Kang, L., Gong, J..2006. Characteristics of mass distributions of aerosol particle and its inorganic water-soluble ions in summer over a suburb farmland in Beijing Environmental Science, 27, 193 - 199</title>
      <link>/en/publication/zhao2006/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/publication/zhao2006/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
