<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Steemitphotochallenge on Peng Zhao</title>
    <link>http://www.pzhao.org/zh/tags/steemitphotochallenge/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Steemitphotochallenge on Peng Zhao</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Peng Zhao</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 22:49:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.pzhao.org/zh/tags/steemitphotochallenge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Holidy in Southern France (V): Coast 带着俩娃游南法 (实时报道第六第七天): 马赛的海岸</title>
      <link>http://www.pzhao.org/zh/post/summer-holidy-in-southern-france-v-coast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 22:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pzhao.org/zh/post/summer-holidy-in-southern-france-v-coast/</guid>
      <description>原文链接: steemit, cnsteem, chainbb, busy, markdown
 The most famous island in Marseille is If owing to Alexandre Dumas&amp;rsquo; adventure novel The Count of Monte Cristo. I would like to pay a one-day visit to this island, but the kids had no interest. They were more interested in the transportation than the destination. I guess that is the difference between adults and kids. Finally we decided to take a cruise to see the coast and islands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Holidy in Southern France (IV): Marseille 带着俩娃游南法 (实时报道第四第五天): 马赛</title>
      <link>http://www.pzhao.org/zh/post/summer-holidy-in-southern-france-iv-marseille/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 22:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pzhao.org/zh/post/summer-holidy-in-southern-france-iv-marseille/</guid>
      <description>原文链接: steemit, cnsteem, chainbb, busy, markdown
Previously on Summer Holiday in Southern France (带着俩娃游南法 前情回顾):
 Day 1: Nice (第一天：尼斯)
 Day 2: Monaco (第二天：摩纳哥)
 Day 3: Cannes (第三天：戛纳)
   On the fourth day we checked out of our family apartment in the morning. As our train from Nice to Marseille was about to set off in the afternoon, we still had some time to see something in Nice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Holidy in Southern France (III): Cannes 带着俩娃游南法 (实时报道第三天): 戛纳</title>
      <link>http://www.pzhao.org/zh/post/summer-holidy-in-southern-france-iii-cannes-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 20:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pzhao.org/zh/post/summer-holidy-in-southern-france-iii-cannes-3/</guid>
      <description>原文链接: steemit, cnsteem, chainbb, busy, markdown
This is a real-time journal of my summer holiday in southern France.
来自南部法国夏日假期的实时报道。
Previously on Summer Holiday in Southern France (带着俩娃游南法 前情回顾):
 Day 1: Nice (第一天：尼斯)
 Day 2: Monaco (第二天：摩纳哥)
   In the previous post I mentioned that I had been confused with Monaco and Morocco. It was not the only case. Besides, I had been confused with Cannes and Ghana as well because of the confusing translations in Chinese.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Holidy in Southern France (II): Monaco 带着俩娃游南法 (2): 摩纳哥</title>
      <link>http://www.pzhao.org/zh/post/summer-holidy-in-southern-france-ii-monoca-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 22:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pzhao.org/zh/post/summer-holidy-in-southern-france-ii-monoca-2/</guid>
      <description>原文链接: steemit, cnsteem, chainbb, busy, markdown
 Previously on Summer Holiday in Southern France:
  &amp;gt; Day 1: Nice  带着俩娃游南法 前情回顾：
 第1天: 尼斯   To save money, we booked a family hotel in Nice at a relatively low price: 110 Euro per day. It was cheap for some reasons. The hotel was located close to the railway station. There was a bar nearby and we could hear people talking and laughing loudly at midnight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer Holidy in Southern France (I): Nice 带着俩娃游南法 (1)：尼斯</title>
      <link>http://www.pzhao.org/zh/post/summer-holidy-in-southern-france-i-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 21:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pzhao.org/zh/post/summer-holidy-in-southern-france-i-1/</guid>
      <description>原文链接: steemit, cnsteem, chainbb, busy, markdown
 Hi everyone. I am now in Southern France for a summer holiday with my family. This is a real time report about this trip. &amp;mdash; Well, maybe not that real, &amp;lsquo;cause I got no time to write anything until now!
 这几天，全家带着俩娃去南部法国度假，这里是我的现场实时报道。这次旅行我原本是不太赞同的，带着两个孩子，大人肯定不会尽兴，而对孩子来说也许还不如去门口的儿童乐园玩得开心。然而，媳妇觉得应该趁暑假多带孩子出去看看，增加一些阅历，同时增加一些开学后跟同学之间的谈资。再说，如果将来回了国，再来玩就更费事了。于是，媳妇就张罗了这一次的暑期南法游。
带着俩娃游南法，到底是休闲还是受罪？我们拭目以待。
Day 1. Nice 尼斯  We started off in Innsbruck with a flight to Frankfurt, and then transfered to another flight to Nice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>