<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post on Peng Zhao</title>
    <link>/en/tags/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post on Peng Zhao</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Peng Zhao</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/en/tags/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest</title>
      <link>/en/home/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/home/posts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A template for Copernicus academic journals</title>
      <link>/en/post/bookdown-copernicus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/bookdown-copernicus/</guid>
      <description>This is a submission to the 1st bookdown contest.
Highlights  Write academic papers of Copernicus journals with R markdown syntax. Support ~ 40 Copernicus journals. Support both the two-columned pdf version and the discussion version. Create multiple file formats, including .pdf, single .html, gitbook, .md, .epub, docx.  Introduction Copernicus Publications is a publisher of scientific literature which publishes around 40 peer-reviewed open access scientific journals and other publications on behalf of the European Geosciences Union (EGU).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A template for MDPI academic journals</title>
      <link>/en/post/bookdown-mdpi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/bookdown-mdpi/</guid>
      <description>This is a submission to the 1st bookdown contest.
Highlights  Write academic papers in the layout of MDPI journals with R markdown syntax. Support ~ 200 MDPI journals. Create multiple file formats, including .pdf, single .html, gitbook, .md, .epub, docx.  Introduction Last year, one of my papers was published on the academic journal atmosphere, which belongs to the Multidisciplinary Digital Publishing Institute (MDPI). To be honest, this draft was written in Microsoft Word, although MDPI provides a nice LaTeX template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Achievements by R bookdown</title>
      <link>/en/post/gource/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/gource/</guid>
      <description>This post is presenting two achievements by bookdown.
The first one is a paper book I wrote: Learning R: R for Rookies (in Chinese). It was published in May 2018 in Mainland China by the Research Publishing Press. I guess it must be the first ever published paper book written in Chinese and built in the bookdown environment. Hooray!
I tried using MS Word at the beginning but I failed. The publishing press tried using Adobe InDesign for typesetting and publishing this book but failed as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meanings of country names in Chinese</title>
      <link>/en/post/country-names/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/country-names/</guid>
      <description>Susan, a friend of mine, comes from Germany. One day, she asked me,excitedly: &amp;lsquo;I heard that Germany in Chinese means a Land of Virtue. Is that true?&amp;rsquo;
&amp;lsquo;True.&amp;rsquo; I said, &amp;lsquo;DEGUO, Country of Virtue.&amp;rsquo;
&amp;lsquo;I love Chinese! Tell me more. What is France in Chinese?&amp;rsquo;
&amp;ndash; &amp;lsquo;FAGUO, Legal Country.&amp;rsquo;
&amp;lsquo;Hm, it makes sense. How about America?&amp;rsquo;
&amp;ndash; &amp;lsquo;MEIGUO, Beautiful Country.&amp;rsquo;
&amp;lsquo;Really? and Britain?&amp;rsquo;
&amp;ndash; &amp;lsquo;YINGJILI, Lucky flowers.&amp;rsquo;
&amp;lsquo;Funny! and the Netherlands?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R package beginr released on CRAN</title>
      <link>/en/post/beginr-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/beginr-released/</guid>
      <description>I’m glad to announce that ‘beginr’ (Zhao 2017) is now on CRAN. This post is a brief documentation of ‘beginr 0.1.0’. Subsequent updates can be found on the GitHub site of beginr.
Introduction‘beginr’ is a collection of useful functions for R beginners, including hints for the arguments of the ‘plot()’ function, self-defined functions for error bars, user-customized pair plots and hist plots, enhanced linear regression figures, etc.. This package could be helpful to R experts as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R package bookdownplus 1.0.2 released on CRAN</title>
      <link>/en/post/bookdownplus-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/bookdownplus-released/</guid>
      <description>I’m glad to announce that ‘bookdownplus 1.0.2’ (Zhao 2017) is now on CRAN. This post is a brief documentation of ‘bookdownplus 1.0.2’. However, I have been updating ‘bookdownplus’ frequently and the new version is more powerful and even easier. Please go to the GitHub site of bookdownplus.
IntroductionThe R package bookdownplus is an extension of bookdown (Xie 2016). It is a collection of multiple templates on the basis of LaTeX, which are tailored so that I can work happily under the umbrella of bookdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LaTeX equations in micrometeorology</title>
      <link>/en/post/equations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/equations/</guid>
      <description>I have collected plenty of equations in my research in recent years. Most of them were typed by my own hands. For convenience, I organized them in an ASCII file named eq.tex as an equation library, side by side with a compiled file named eq.pdf. When I needed an equation, I searched eq.pdf, and looked for the codes in eq.tex, and then copied and posted it to my working document. A little annoying, but much better than retyping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R package mindr: convert markdown files to mind maps, and vice versa</title>
      <link>/en/post/mindr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/mindr/</guid>
      <description>This is a preliminary version of the introduction to mindr. Please go to my Github repo mindr for the latest updates.
Quick startInstallationdevtools::install_github(&amp;quot;pzhaonet/mindr&amp;quot;)Convert (a) markdown file(s) into a mindmapCreate a folder named mm in the working directory (getwd()), and drop some markdown or rmarkdown files into mm/. Run:
mindr::md2mm()then you will get a mm.mm file. Open it with any mind-map (brainstorm) software, and you will get a mind map.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R package postr: created posters with R markdown</title>
      <link>/en/post/postr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/postr/</guid>
      <description>This is a preliminary version of the introduction to postr. Please go to my Github repo postr for the latest updates.
This package is modified from kuleuven-template, where you can see the requirements before using this package. Here I picked out the instruction for Windows users as follows.
Install a LaTeX distribution, e.g. MiKTeX. For Chinese users CTeX is highly recommended.Install TexmakerInstall RInstall RStudioInstall Python 2Install Python filter support for Pandoc: on a Windows command prompt, type pip install pandocfiltersInstall SumatraPDF for auto-refresh of PDF previewsAfterwards, add the Python directory to the system PATH variable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bookdownplus: an R package for writing Articles, Mails, Guitar Chords, Chemical Molecular Formulae and Equations with R bookdown</title>
      <link>/en/post/bookdownplus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/bookdownplus/</guid>
      <description>This is a preliminary version of the introduction to bookdownplus. Please go to my Github repo bookdownplus for the latest updates. Full documentation can be found in the book R bookdownplus Textbook.
IntroductionR bookdownplus is an extension of R bookdown (Xie 2016). It is a collection of multiple templates on the basis of LaTeX, which are tailored so that I can work happily under the umbrella of bookdown. R bookdownplus helps you write academic journal articles, guitar books, chemical equations, mails, calendars, and diaries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R bookdown cheatsheet</title>
      <link>/en/post/bookdown-cheatsheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/bookdown-cheatsheet/</guid>
      <description>Quick StartWhat is R bookdownA software for writing books or documents.More elegant than MS Word. Much easier than \(\LaTeX\).Users can easily insert table of contents, figures and tables with cross-reference, footnotes, and index.Users can easily embed equations, citations, R scripts.pdf, word and html files can be exported.best choice to write reproducible documents.InstallationDownload R and install it.Download RStudio and install it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>