<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bookdown on Peng Zhao</title>
    <link>/en/tags/bookdown/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bookdown on Peng Zhao</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Peng Zhao</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/en/tags/bookdown/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>R package bookdownplus 1.0.2 released on CRAN</title>
      <link>/en/post/bookdownplus-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/bookdownplus-released/</guid>
      <description>I’m glad to announce that ‘bookdownplus 1.0.2’ (Zhao 2017) is now on CRAN. This post is a brief documentation of ‘bookdownplus 1.0.2’. However, I have been updating ‘bookdownplus’ frequently and the new version is more powerful and even easier. Please go to the GitHub site of bookdownplus.
IntroductionThe R package bookdownplus is an extension of bookdown (Xie 2016). It is a collection of multiple templates on the basis of LaTeX, which are tailored so that I can work happily under the umbrella of bookdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bookdownplus: an R package for writing Articles, Mails, Guitar Chords, Chemical Molecular Formulae and Equations with R bookdown</title>
      <link>/en/post/bookdownplus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/bookdownplus/</guid>
      <description>This is a preliminary version of the introduction to bookdownplus. Please go to my Github repo bookdownplus for the latest updates. Full documentation can be found in the book R bookdownplus Textbook.
IntroductionR bookdownplus is an extension of R bookdown (Xie 2016). It is a collection of multiple templates on the basis of LaTeX, which are tailored so that I can work happily under the umbrella of bookdown. R bookdownplus helps you write academic journal articles, guitar books, chemical equations, mails, calendars, and diaries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R bookdown cheatsheet</title>
      <link>/en/post/bookdown-cheatsheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/post/bookdown-cheatsheet/</guid>
      <description>Quick StartWhat is R bookdownA software for writing books or documents.More elegant than MS Word. Much easier than \(\LaTeX\).Users can easily insert table of contents, figures and tables with cross-reference, footnotes, and index.Users can easily embed equations, citations, R scripts.pdf, word and html files can be exported.best choice to write reproducible documents.InstallationDownload R and install it.Download RStudio and install it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>