<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutorial on Peng Zhao</title>
    <link>http://www.pzhao.org/zh/tags/tutorial/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tutorial on Peng Zhao</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Peng Zhao</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 21:04:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.pzhao.org/zh/tags/tutorial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Steemit Tips: One single click to batch resize and compress images, and insert your watermark 一键批量压缩多张图片和批量插入水印</title>
      <link>http://www.pzhao.org/zh/post/steemit-tips-one-single-click-to-batch-resize-and-compress-images-and-insert-your-watermark/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 21:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pzhao.org/zh/post/steemit-tips-one-single-click-to-batch-resize-and-compress-images-and-insert-your-watermark/</guid>
      <description>原文链接: steemit, cnsteem, chainbb, busy, markdown
The photographs taken by your camera or smartphone are usually unnecessarily large for posting on Steemit. They do nothing but slow down the loading of your post when others browse your post and waste their time. They might lose their patience and close your post. If the images are resized to figures with the width of 800 pixels before uploading, the size could be 10% of the original size, or even smaller, without losing any visual effect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steemit Tips: Create your Steemit watermark using Powerpoint 制作你的专属 Steemit 透明背景水印</title>
      <link>http://www.pzhao.org/zh/post/steemit-tips-create-your-steemit-watermark-using-powerpoint-steemit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 20:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.pzhao.org/zh/post/steemit-tips-create-your-steemit-watermark-using-powerpoint-steemit/</guid>
      <description>原文链接: steemit, cnsteem, chainbb, busy, markdown
Some friends asked me how to make a Steemit ID watermark with a transparent background, like this.
有朋友问我的 Steemit ID 的透明背景水印图片是如何制作的，就像下图：
The point is the transparent background. It means, the watermark looks like this when inserted into a picture:
关键点在于背景是透明的，这样的话，插入到图片里不会出现一个白色矩形：
It is easy. You do not have to use Photoshop. Powerpoint can do it. Here is the procedure. An animation gif is given at the end of this post as well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>